finallyfast.com 2015-04-03

# FinallyFast.com - Privacy Policy

## Ascentive's Privacy Policy

The following discloses our information gathering and usage practices.

We may share your unique identifying information with outside parties when they are helping us fulfill your order. We have safeguards in place (strong encryption, passwords, and limited access policies) to protect your information on our systems and when being communicated to our order fulfillment partners, such as the shipping warehouse.

We use a cookie so you don't see our pop-up offer more than once per day. The cookie contains the date you saw our popup. If you have disabled cookies in your web browser, you'll see our popup offer every time you exit our web site. Ascentive applications may send anonymous usage data to Ascentive LLC. We use this information to track visitors' movement in the aggregate, and to gather general information about which screens are being accessed to improve the overall customer experience.

Ascentive's Revenue Partners program provide site traffic to www.ascentive.com in exchange for a percentage of sales revenue. When you order an Ascentive product and you have been referred by a Revenue Partner, the following anonymous information is provided to the Revenue Partner to calculate revenue and verify our compliance: order number, product name, product cost, and date/time. **No customer identifying information is provided to Revenue Partners unless that Revenue Partner is responsible for helping us fulfill your order, in which case your personal information will only be used by Revenue Partner to fulfill your order.** Ascentive is not responsible for information you choose to provide directly to an Ascentive Revenue Partner via their web site.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Financial information that is collected is used to bill the customer for products and services. Miscellaneous optional information collected on the order form, such as connection speed and operating system, are used in aggregate to help us make decisions about developing new products and services. Contact information you provide on your order form may be used occasionally by Ascentive or select partners to announce free updates to software items ordered, special offers and related promotions. You may opt out of this at any time. We are committed to respecting your wishes for use of your personal data.

Software for mobile devices may include additional software and/or functionality for to report to Ascentive and/or one or more third parties certain analytical data regarding your use of the applicable software (collectively, “Analytical Data”).  All third party providers that analyze, collect, receive or process Analtical Data from us or on our behalf are prohibited from using such Analytical Data except on our behalf.  All Analytical Data that is collected by Ascentive will be used only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Ascentive uses passwords and SSL encryption to protect the security of this information.

**Other Ascentive Software**  
Our software may include links or recommendations for other Ascentive products that would complement your current purchase. If you decide to activate an account and provide us with your email address, you will be automatically subscribed to receive Ascentive’s periodic newsletter (SpeedElite) in the form of an html email, with information including, but not limited to, software updates, discount offers, and new software releases. If you do not wish to receive these announcements, you can remove your name from our mailing list by the unsubscribe process detailed at the bottom of each newsletter or contact Ascentive LLC via our web site at www.ascentive.com and request to be removed from our list. Ascentive LLC does not sell or trade customer information. Any customer contact information is kept private and never given out or sold to a third party.

**Correct/Update**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

  * You can send us email at the [Ascentive Support Center](http://www.ascentive.com/support/).
  * You can send mail to the following postal address: 

Ascentive LLC,  
50 S. 16th Street ,  
Philadelphia, PA 19102  

You can call the following telephone number: 1.215.320.6000

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

Ascentive Webmaster,  
50 S. 16th Street,  
Philadelphia, PA 19102
